

RAEES BRENE —— DEVELOPER ——

OVERVIEW

I'm a developer with at least 2 years of experience developing web solutions using technologies ranging from drag and drop technologies such as wix, glideapps, Adobe XD and figma to programming with HTML, CSS, SCSS, Python & JavaScript

CONTACT

(+27)78 613 2128

<u>rbrene786@gmail.com</u>

raeesbrene.com

SKILLS

HTML5

5

CSS3 SCSS

dj Js

Python Django JavaScript

⊗ Xd ₿

React.js Adobe XD Figma

REFERENCES

ANGELO KING

angelo@rlabs.org (+27) 76 158 4855

TARYN ABRAHAMS

taryn@rlabs.org (+27) 76 925 3221

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

COLLEGE OF CAPE TOWN

Information Technology & Computer Science

2019

FREECODECAMP

JavaScript Algorithms & Data Structures 2019

FREECODECAMP

Responsive Web Design

2020

COURSERA

Google IT Automation with Python

EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2020

DIGITAL ARTISAN

RECONSTRUCTED LIVING LABS

Developed web and mobile front-end solutions using development tools & technologies such as glideapps for mobile and wix, HTML, CSS and JavaScript for web. 2020 - 2021

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

RECONSTRUCTED LIVING LABS

Lead a team of interns to develop web solutions using the django web framework and facilitate their skills development and gain valuable work experience.